[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120609pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 123, "question": "What was it like to see your son elected president?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "it", "like", "to", "see", "your", "son", "elected", "president", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 124, "answer": "Very emotional for me.", "answer_tokens": ["Very", "emotional", "for", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120609pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "CC", ":", "WRB", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 145, "question": "You, as his friend, what do you think?", "question_tokens": ["You", ",", "as", "his", "friend", ",", "what", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 146, "answer": "I think he felt badly for his son, and -- when his son was criticized.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "he", "felt", "badly", "for", "his", "son", ",", "and", "--", "when", "his", "son", "was", "criticized", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120609pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 219, "question": "?", "question_tokens": ["?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["."], "aSentId": 220, "answer": "You know, I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120609pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 230, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 231, "answer": "Yeah, I think so.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", ",", "I", "think", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120609pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 253, "question": "Chaz, how are you?", "question_tokens": ["Chaz", ",", "how", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 254, "answer": "I'm good.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "good", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120609pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "TO", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "WP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 255, "question": "How are you doing?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", "doing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 256, "answer": "Well, I was just trying to think back to our last encounter, and what an extraordinary twist to your life that's gone on ever since.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "was", "just", "trying", "to", "think", "back", "to", "our", "last", "encounter", ",", "and", "what", "an", "extraordinary", "twist", "to", "your", "life", "that", "'s", "gone", "on", "ever", "since", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120609pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 273, "question": "How much pressure did the fact that you had decided to become a man -- how much pressure did that put on the relationship, do you think, looking back?", "question_tokens": ["How", "much", "pressure", "did", "the", "fact", "that", "you", "had", "decided", "to", "become", "a", "man", "--", "how", "much", "pressure", "did", "that", "put", "on", "the", "relationship", ",", "do", "you", "think", ",", "looking", "back", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", ":", "WRB", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 274, "answer": "I mean, I think it put some pressure on the relationship.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "I", "think", "it", "put", "some", "pressure", "on", "the", "relationship", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120609pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 282, "question": "Did you feel that she ever fully embraced what you were doing?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "feel", "that", "she", "ever", "fully", "embraced", "what", "you", "were", "doing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 283, "answer": "You know, I think that she did.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "think", "that", "she", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120609pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 291, "question": "Do you regret doing that, with hindsight?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "regret", "doing", "that", ",", "with", "hindsight", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "IN", ",", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 292, "answer": "I mean, it wasn't a pleasant thing to do, you know, honestly.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "it", "was", "n't", "a", "pleasant", "thing", "to", "do", ",", "you", "know", ",", "honestly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120609pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 298, "question": "Have you managed to stay friends?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "managed", "to", "stay", "friends", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 299, "answer": "Yeah I mean, I think we both cared very deeply for each other.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "I", "mean", ",", "I", "think", "we", "both", "cared", "very", "deeply", "for", "each", "other", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120609pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "RBS", "VBG", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 305, "question": "How are you finding that?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", "finding", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 306, "answer": "Well, you know, I'm not the most outgoing fellow.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "'m", "not", "the", "most", "outgoing", "fellow", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120609pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "RB", ":", "WRB", "IN", "JJ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 338, "question": "What did you feel when all that bile was being spilled in your direction?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "feel", "when", "all", "that", "bile", "was", "being", "spilled", "in", "your", "direction", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "DT", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "VBG", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 339, "answer": "You know, I think that it just -- when that first started with those type of people, I just kind of let it roll off my back.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "think", "that", "it", "just", "--", "when", "that", "first", "started", "with", "those", "type", "of", "people", ",", "I", "just", "kind", "of", "let", "it", "roll", "off", "my", "back", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["White House"]}, "docId": "120609pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", ":", "CC", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNP", "NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 357, "question": "If he becomes president, would that concern you to his position on, as you said, a new civil rights issue in many ways would be pretty intransigent?", "question_tokens": ["If", "he", "becomes", "president", ",", "would", "that", "concern", "you", "to", "his", "position", "on", ",", "as", "you", "said", ",", "a", "new", "civil", "rights", "issue", "in", "many", "ways", "would", "be", "pretty", "intransigent", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", ",", "MD", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 358, "answer": "You know, as a Democrat I'm always -- and especially after our last Republican president -- I'm concerned to have a Republican in the White House for any number of reason.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "as", "a", "Democrat", "I", "'m", "always", "--", "and", "especially", "after", "our", "last", "Republican", "president", "--", "I", "'m", "concerned", "to", "have", "a", "Republican", "in", "the", "White", "House", "for", "any", "number", "of", "reason", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120609pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 359, "question": "But particularly that one?", "question_tokens": ["But", "particularly", "that", "one", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "IN", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 360, "answer": "I get -- any number of reasons.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "get", "--", "any", "number", "of", "reasons", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120609pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 363, "question": "Do you and your stepmother have lively debates about this, Chaz?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "and", "your", "stepmother", "have", "lively", "debates", "about", "this", ",", "Chaz", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 364, "answer": "You know, we really -- we really don't.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "we", "really", "--", "we", "really", "do", "n't", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Chaz?"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120609pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 406, "question": "How excited are you about London?", "question_tokens": ["How", "excited", "are", "you", "about", "London", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBN", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 407, "answer": "You know, I'm very excited.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "'m", "very", "excited", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["London"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120609pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 417, "question": "Why not?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "not", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 418, "answer": "No, no.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120609pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 434, "question": "Like what the heck?", "question_tokens": ["Like", "what", "the", "heck", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 435, "answer": "That's the picture there.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "the", "picture", "there", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120609pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 438, "question": "What happened?", "question_tokens": ["What", "happened", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 439, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120609pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 440, "question": "In the last hundredth of a second did you just give up?", "question_tokens": ["In", "the", "last", "hundredth", "of", "a", "second", "did", "you", "just", "give", "up", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 441, "answer": "No, I didn't give up.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "did", "n't", "give", "up", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120609pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 445, "question": "Seriously?", "question_tokens": ["Seriously", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 446, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120609pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 448, "question": "You went and broke your thumb?", "question_tokens": ["You", "went", "and", "broke", "your", "thumb", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "CC", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 449, "answer": "I broke my thumb in the next race.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "broke", "my", "thumb", "in", "the", "next", "race", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120609pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", ":", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 450, "question": "Because you were so full of rage?", "question_tokens": ["Because", "you", "were", "so", "full", "of", "rage", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 451, "answer": "I was just -- I couldn't believe I lost by a touch.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "just", "--", "I", "could", "n't", "believe", "I", "lost", "by", "a", "touch", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120609pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 452, "question": "How hard are you hitting that wall to break your thumb?", "question_tokens": ["How", "hard", "are", "you", "hitting", "that", "wall", "to", "break", "your", "thumb", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 453, "answer": "I didn't know I did it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "did", "n't", "know", "I", "did", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120609pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 462, "question": "No man?", "question_tokens": ["No", "man", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 463, "answer": "That's a good question.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "a", "good", "question", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120609pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 468, "question": "Which one are you going to take?", "question_tokens": ["Which", "one", "are", "you", "going", "to", "take", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "CD", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 469, "answer": "Oh, my gosh.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "my", "gosh", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120609pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "JJR", "."], "qSentId": 488, "question": "Is that true?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "true", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 489, "answer": "I think I have to shut my mouth more.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "I", "have", "to", "shut", "my", "mouth", "more", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120609pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "NNS", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 508, "question": "Next?", "question_tokens": ["Next", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "."], "aSentId": 509, "answer": "I always quaintly assumed that when you get to that stage of the preparation it's like boxers, there's no hanky-panky.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "always", "quaintly", "assumed", "that", "when", "you", "get", "to", "that", "stage", "of", "the", "preparation", "it", "'s", "like", "boxers", ",", "there", "'s", "no", "hanky-panky", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120609pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 518, "question": "So why not, right?", "question_tokens": ["So", "why", "not", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "RB", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 519, "answer": "Of course, I never did anything like that.", "answer_tokens": ["Of", "course", ",", "I", "never", "did", "anything", "like", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120609pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 520, "question": "Did you have your eyes on anybody special this year after -- say you win gold, anyone on the American Olympic squad that you might be the lucky recipient of my joy?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "have", "your", "eyes", "on", "anybody", "special", "this", "year", "after", "--", "say", "you", "win", "gold", ",", "anyone", "on", "the", "American", "Olympic", "squad", "that", "you", "might", "be", "the", "lucky", "recipient", "of", "my", "joy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "IN", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", ",", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 521, "answer": "I'm as old as their mothers.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "as", "old", "as", "their", "mothers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120609pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 535, "question": "Are we going to stand side by side and do it together?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "we", "going", "to", "stand", "side", "by", "side", "and", "do", "it", "together", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 536, "answer": "No, we're not.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "we", "'re", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120609pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNS", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 549, "question": "OK, let's get to -- women watch this, falling over saying how, how do you keep that six pack looking like that?", "question_tokens": ["OK", ",", "let", "'s", "get", "to", "--", "women", "watch", "this", ",", "falling", "over", "saying", "how", ",", "how", "do", "you", "keep", "that", "six", "pack", "looking", "like", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", ",", "VB", "POS", "NN", "TO", ":", "NNS", "VBP", "DT", ",", "VBG", "IN", "VBG", "WRB", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "CD", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 550, "answer": "Well, people have to remember I do this for a living.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "people", "have", "to", "remember", "I", "do", "this", "for", "a", "living", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120609pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "CD", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 553, "question": "For how long?", "question_tokens": ["For", "how", "long", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 554, "answer": "Probably between four and six hours.", "answer_tokens": ["Probably", "between", "four", "and", "six", "hours", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120609pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 557, "question": "Where do you get your information from?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "do", "you", "get", "your", "information", "from", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 558, "answer": "I've just done a very thorough research job on you.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ve", "just", "done", "a", "very", "thorough", "research", "job", "on", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120609pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 577, "question": "So did you fire him?", "question_tokens": ["So", "did", "you", "fire", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 578, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120609pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 581, "question": "What has he said about London?", "question_tokens": ["What", "has", "he", "said", "about", "London", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 582, "answer": "I don't like to share that, because I don't want to jinx anything.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "like", "to", "share", "that", ",", "because", "I", "do", "n't", "want", "to", "jinx", "anything", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["London"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120609pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 585, "question": "It'll stay between us?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'ll", "stay", "between", "us", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 586, "answer": "And hundreds of millions of people around the world.", "answer_tokens": ["And", "hundreds", "of", "millions", "of", "people", "around", "the", "world", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120609pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 587, "question": "What has he got right?", "question_tokens": ["What", "has", "he", "got", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 588, "answer": "He's gotten a lot right about my personal life.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "'s", "gotten", "a", "lot", "right", "about", "my", "personal", "life", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120609pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 589, "question": "Like what?", "question_tokens": ["Like", "what", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 590, "answer": "Well, okay.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "okay", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120609pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 593, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 594, "answer": "Yeah, yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", ",", "yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120609pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 596, "question": "You were having trouble conceiving and he predicted you would have a daughter?", "question_tokens": ["You", "were", "having", "trouble", "conceiving", "and", "he", "predicted", "you", "would", "have", "a", "daughter", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "NN", "VBG", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 597, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120609pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "EX", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "CD", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "CC", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 605, "question": "Who does he talk to?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "does", "he", "talk", "to", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "."], "aSentId": 606, "answer": "Well, what you do is you go in there and he leaves the room and you take a card and you write down three questions that you want answered and your write down three people who have passed away and you sign and print your name.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "what", "you", "do", "is", "you", "go", "in", "there", "and", "he", "leaves", "the", "room", "and", "you", "take", "a", "card", "and", "you", "write", "down", "three", "questions", "that", "you", "want", "answered", "and", "your", "write", "down", "three", "people", "who", "have", "passed", "away", "and", "you", "sign", "and", "print", "your", "name", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120609pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", ":", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "WRB", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "IN", "VBN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 616, "question": "And you have a conversation through this man?", "question_tokens": ["And", "you", "have", "a", "conversation", "through", "this", "man", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 617, "answer": "ORRES: I don't have a conversation -- yeah, he's an example, I asked something and my dad came in and he started talking about how my dad only wants me to finish this last one because he wants to see me have a family and you know have that come first.", "answer_tokens": ["ORRES", ":", "I", "do", "n't", "have", "a", "conversation", "--", "yeah", ",", "he", "'s", "an", "example", ",", "I", "asked", "something", "and", "my", "dad", "came", "in", "and", "he", "started", "talking", "about", "how", "my", "dad", "only", "wants", "me", "to", "finish", "this", "last", "one", "because", "he", "wants", "to", "see", "me", "have", "a", "family", "and", "you", "know", "have", "that", "come", "first", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120609pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 632, "question": "Until that's done in your life, do you think you've got a chance?", "question_tokens": ["Until", "that", "'s", "done", "in", "your", "life", ",", "do", "you", "think", "you", "'ve", "got", "a", "chance", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 633, "answer": "Well, I guess I'll find out in a few months.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "guess", "I", "'ll", "find", "out", "in", "a", "few", "months", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120609pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "MD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 638, "question": "So one last gold in London?", "question_tokens": ["So", "one", "last", "gold", "in", "London", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "CD", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 639, "answer": "I actually would just like to make the Olympic team.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "actually", "would", "just", "like", "to", "make", "the", "Olympic", "team", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["London"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120609pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 641, "question": "They will won't you?", "question_tokens": ["They", "will", "wo", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 642, "answer": "I hope so.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "hope", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]